Guide to the Records of the Office of the Treasurer RG.10.2
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the Treasurer
1896-1982
1900-1960
New York University Archives
New York University. Office of the Treasurer
RG.10.2
14 Linear Feet
This collection contains annual reports and financial reports created by the Office of the Treasurer. The collection also contains surveyor's maps, drawings, and blueprints from the Bursar's Office at NYU's University Heights campus.
Provenance
The collection was transferred to the University Archives from the Office of the Treasurer in multiple accessions.
In May 2024, approximately 20 maps and blueprints of the University Heights campus and some maps of New York City's public transport system was transferred from the New York University Archives Photograph Collection (PHOTO 00001). The accession number associated with this accretion is 2024.039.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Please contact the University Archivists with specific questions regarding restrictions.
Historical Note
The Office of the Treasurer, now called the Office of Finance, is responsible for financing transactions, the University's relation with banks, management of short-term cash, overseeing the Bursar's Office and Insurance Department, and processing gifts to the University.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains annual reports and financial reports created by the Office of the Treasurer. The collection also contains surveyor's maps, drawings, and blueprints from the Bursar's Office at NYU's University Heights campus.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged by date.
The files are grouped into two series:
Series I: Reports
Series II: Maps and Blueprints
Reports.; Universities and Colleges -- Finance; Maps.; blueprints (reprographic copies); Transportation.; Construction projects.; New York University -- Administration
- Series I: Reports, 1896-1982
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains annual reports and financial reports created by the Office of the Treasurer.
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Barcode #: 3 1142 042267628
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226762 8
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226763 6
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226764 4
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226765 1
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NYU Financial Report (25 copies), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - NYU Financial Report (22 copies), 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226766 9
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (2 copies), 1938-1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (3 copies), 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (2 copies), 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (4 copies), 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226767 7
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (5 copies), 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (5 copies), 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (5 copies), 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (10 copies), 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226768 5
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (3 copies), 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (8 copies), 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (6 copies), 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the Chancellor - Financial Report, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the President, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1916-1917 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226769 3
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1922-1923 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1923-1924 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1924-1925 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NYU Reports of the Chancellor and Treasurer, 1925-1926 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1925-1926 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1931-1932 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (2 copies), 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (2 copies), 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (2 copies), 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - NYU Gift Report (2 copies), 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - NYU Gift Report (5 copies), 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226770 1
  - NYU Gift Report (5 copies), 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NYU Gift Report (5 copies), 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the President (2 copies), 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the President (3 copies), 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the President (3 copies), 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the President (3 copies), 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the President (3 copies), 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the President (3 copies), 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - NYU Financial Report (4 copies), 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer for the Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer for the Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer for the Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (9 copies), 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (5 copies), 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226771 9
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the President - Financial Report (5 copies), 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1920-1921 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1921-1922 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1923-1924 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer, 1924-1925 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (3 copies), 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NYU Reports of the Chancellor and Treasurer (2 copies), 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1926-1927 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (4 copies), 1924-1925 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226772 7
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1932-1933 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (1 copy), 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (5 copies), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (3 copies), 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - NYU Report of the Treasurer (4 copies), 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226773 5
  - Life Insurance and Retirement Payments - 3 vols., undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1911-1912 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1912-1913 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1913-1914 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1914-1915 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1915-1916 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1916-1917 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1917-1918 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1918-1919 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1896-1898 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226774 3
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1899 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1900 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1901 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1902 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1904 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1906 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1907 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1908 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - NYU Statement of Treasurer, 1909 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - University of the City of New York - Donor Solicitations for founding of University - v.3, 1830 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - University of the City of New York - Donor Solicitations for founding of University - v.4, 1830 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - University of the City of New York - Donor Solicitations for founding of University - v.5, 1830 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - University of the City of New York - Donor Solicitations for founding of University - v.6, 1830 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - University of the City of New York - Donor Solicitations for founding of University - v.11, 1830 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - University of the City of New York - Donor Solicitations for founding of University - v.16, 1830 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Bond Receipt Book - 7/1/1920 - 6/30/1925, 1920-1925 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NYU Gift Report, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - NYU Gift Report, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - NYU Financial Report (3 copies), 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Series II: Maps and Blueprints, 1914-1955
  This series contains surveyor's maps, drawings, and blueprints from the Bursar's Office at NYU's University Heights campus.
  - Maps of University Heights Campus and University Avenue, 1914 (Box Shared University Archives 149, Folder 17)
  - Survey Maps of Weigand Place, 1922 (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 13)
  - Maps of University Heights Campus, 1924, 1927, 1930 (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 14)
  - Surveyor's Map for Widening of Sedgwick Avenue, 1931 (Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 12)
  - Surveyor's Map of University Heights Campus, University Avenue, West 180th Street, and Weigand Place, 1933 (Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 12)
  - New York City Public Transport Maps, 1955 (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 12)
  - Blueprints for Private Garage at University Heights Campus, undated (Box Shared University Archives 150, Folder 5)